[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
As we've seen, overfitting decision trees is a fundamental problem that must be
وكما شاهدنا، فإن التطابق المفرط في شجر القرار، يُعد مشكلة أساسية
addressed.
يجب عرضها.
And we've looked at a couple different ways to address this problem.
ولقد تفحصنا طريقتين مختلفتين لعرض هذه المشكلة.
We looked at early stopping.
وتناولنا التوقف المبكر
So as we go down the tree,
لذا وبنزولنا إلى أسفل الشجرة،
we're going to stop early to avoid getting to a very complex tree and overfitting.
سنقوم بالتوقف المبكر لتلافي مواجهة شجرة معقدة جدًا أو تطابق مفرط.
And then we talked about pruning, where we take a massive tree and then we chop,
وكما تحدثنا عن التقليم،حيث تناولنا شجرة ضخمة
chop, chop, chop and simplify it.
ومن ثم بدأنا نقلم ونقلم ونقلم حتى بسطناها.
Pruning is very important in practical settings, and so
يعد التقليم هامًا جدًا في الممارسات العملية
we spent quite a of bit of time going through the details of that but
ولذا قضينا قليل من الوقت نستكشف تفاصيل ذلك
it was optional section in the lecture.
ولكن ذلك كان مقطعًا اختياريًا في المحاضرة.
But I just want to make sure,
ولكني فقط أردت التأكد،
we're all aware that if you see an algorithm out there for
أننا جميعا على دراية، بأننا إن شاهدنا خوارزمية موجودة لشجر القرار
decision trees that does pruning, that's a kind of idea of what's being executed.
يتم تقليمها، فهذا نبذة عما يتم تنفيذه.
So overfitting decision trees is a fundamental topic, but
لذا فإن التطابق المفرط لشجر القرار، يعد موضوعًا أساسيًا
one that now we have a handle on how to address.
ولكنه واحدًا من المواضيع التي يمكننا استيعاب كيفية عرضها.
And let me close by thanking my colleague, Krishna Sridhar,
ودعوني أختتم بشكر زميلي، كريشنا سريدهار
who has been really fundamental at creating these slides and
والذي قدم الكثير لإنشاء تلك الشرائح
being able to make this lecture as great as possible.
واستطاع جعل هذه المحاضرة على النحو الأمثل.
[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]